var questions = [
{

"question": "Choose the odd one out.",

"option1": "csh",

"option2": "bsh",

"option3": "ksh",

"option4": "Kernel",

"answer" : "4",
},

{

"question": "What is the option to create symbolic link for a file?",

"option1": "–s",

"option2": "–l",

"option3": "–f",

"option4": "None of the above.",

"answer" : "1",
},


{

"question": "What is the option to create hard link for a directory?",

"option1": "–s",

"option2": "–l",

"option3": "–f",

"option4": "None of the above.",

"answer" : "4",
},


{

"question": "The following command can list out all the current active logins.",

"option1": "whoami",

"option2": "who am i",

"option3": "who",

"option4": "None of the above.",

"answer" : "3",
},


{
"question": "Choose the command to print the current working directory",

"option1": "cwd",

"option2": "pwd",

"option3": "wd",

"option4": "nwd",

"answer" : "2",
},


{
"question": "What is the file descriptor number which represents the STDOUT?",

"option1": "0",

"option2": "1",

"option3": "2",

"option4": "None of the above.",

"answer" : "2",
},


{
"question": "What does the following command would do $ cp ../file.",

"option1": "Copies the file from current directory to parent directory",

"option2": "Copies the file from parent directory to its parent directory",

"option3": "Copies the file from parent directory to current directory",

"option4": "Error in the command",

"answer" : "3",

},


{

"question": "Identify the environment variable which designates secondary prompt.",

"option1": "PP1",

"option2": "SP2",

"option3": "PS1",

"option4": "PS2",

"answer" : "4",
},


{

"question": "A process is ___",

"option1": "Collection of threads",

"option2": "A thread",

"option3": "Software",

"option4": "A running program",

"answer" : "4",
},

{

"question": "What is PPID?",

"option1": "Previous process identification",

"option2": "Priority process identification",

"option3": "Parent process identification",

"option4": "Pre Parent identification",

"answer" : "3",
}
]
